<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home Dr Wajid Khan on Dr Wajid Khan, PhD LLM, AI, Data Software Engineer, London, UK.</title>
    <link>https://www.wajidkhan.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home Dr Wajid Khan on Dr Wajid Khan, PhD LLM, AI, Data Software Engineer, London, UK.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:53:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.wajidkhan.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact Dr Wajid Khan</title>
      <link>https://www.wajidkhan.info/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wajidkhan.info/contact/</guid>
      <description>Engage with an AI and LLM Specialist Your journey through the intricate realms of AI, data, and advanced software begins here. I am dedicated to providing personalised attention to each query, ensuring that your unique challenges are met with expert solutions. Embrace the opportunity to delve into AI and data complexities with a seasoned professional.
Contact Information Email: me@wajidkhan.info Direct UK Line # + 44 203 468 2115
Pakistan Line # + 92 937 55 22 34</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Dr Wajid Khan</title>
      <link>https://www.wajidkhan.info/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wajidkhan.info/home/</guid>
      <description>Home Dr. Khan: Pioneering Business Transformation with Advanced Generative-AI Avatars Embark on a journey of innovation with Dr. Khan, a seasoned expert in Generative-AI, grant funding, and contract bidding. His unique blend of skills as an AI specialist, marketing strategist, and business growth leader makes him the go-to advisor for CEOs and CTOs aiming to excel in today&amp;rsquo;s competitive market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LLM, Code &amp; AI Services</title>
      <link>https://www.wajidkhan.info/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wajidkhan.info/services/</guid>
      <description>AI, LLM &amp;amp; Software Mastery Welcome to the forefront of software innovation, where the potential of AI meets expert engineering. As a seasoned software engineer, I specialise in harnessing the power of Large Language Models and AI to create solutions that are advanced and intuitively align with your business needs.
My approach combines deep technical expertise with a keen understanding of AI&amp;rsquo;s transformative capabilities. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s developing custom software solutions, integrating AI to streamline processes, or exploring the vast potential of LLMs, the focus is always on delivering exceptional, user-centric results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
