<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Engineering &amp; AI Digital Marketing on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Engineering &amp; AI Digital Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bespoke Technology HR and Headhunting for Startups</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/technology-team-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/technology-team-building/</guid>
      <description>In the fast-paced world of startups, the right technology team can differentiate between success and stagnation. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re building your MVP or scaling operations, having the right talent mix is crucial.&#xA;Our bespoke Technology HR and Headhunting service is designed to match your unique needs, ensuring your startup is equipped with the best minds in the industry.&#xA;Strategic Talent Acquisition and Headhunting for Key Roles We understand your needs and match you with professionals who can help achieve your goals, specialising in software engineering positions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book A Short Call For Partnerships</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/short-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/short-call/</guid>
      <description>Bridging the gap between innovative software engineering and impactful digital marketing for your brand&amp;rsquo;s success online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Legacy Custom Backend Software Audits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/legacy-custom-software-audits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/legacy-custom-software-audits/</guid>
      <description>In today’s competitive startup landscape, outdated backend systems can be a hidden liability, dragging down performance and valuation.&#xA;Our Comprehensive Legacy Custom Backend Software Audits are designed to uncover these hidden challenges, providing you with a clear path to modernisation and growth.&#xA;Mitigate Risks and Maximise Tech Innovation Potential Our expert team excels in analysing legacy custom backend systems and identifying critical risks and performance bottlenecks.&#xA;We also uncover opportunities to modernise your infrastructure, ensuring your software remains stable, secure, and ready for future scalability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert Startup Technology Evaluation Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/startup-tech-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/startup-tech-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>Our startup technology evaluation services systematically document your business&amp;rsquo;s technological landscape, forming a strategic roadmap crucial for achieving your success goals.&#xA;Evaluating technology effectively allows startups to align their operations with market demands, ensuring a competitive edge and sustained growth.&#xA;The Significance of Technology Evaluation in Startups Effective technology evaluation drives informed decisions, enhancing competitiveness, funding potential, and intellectual property security.&#xA;Aligns technology with business objectives for strategic growth. Identifies risks and opportunities for stronger market positioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Start a Side Hustle in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/side-hustle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/side-hustle/</guid>
      <description>Bridging the gap between innovative software engineering and impactful digital marketing for your brand&amp;rsquo;s success online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Digi-Assets Pools (DAPs) For Search Engines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private-digi-assets-pool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private-digi-assets-pool/</guid>
      <description>Private Digi-Assets Pools For Search Engines&#xA;coming soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research and Interests</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research-and-interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research-and-interests/</guid>
      <description>Interests I am passionate about transforming innovative concepts into thriving businesses, rapidly achieving the first £100k in revenue.&#xA;My focus lies in strategically managing technical debt, recruiting top talent, and cultivating high-performing teams.&#xA;I believe that great software is the foundation of success. It must be crafted to align with the business&amp;rsquo;s operational capabilities, ensuring a decisive competitive advantage.&#xA;Education Doctor of Philosophy (PhD) Information Visualisation and Data Analysis Using AI Systems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service Fees</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/service-fees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/service-fees/</guid>
      <description>Bridging the gap between innovative software engineering and impactful digital marketing for your brand&amp;rsquo;s success online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineering &amp; AI Digital Marketing Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/</guid>
      <description>Embarking on a digital journey? I’m here, ready to guide SMEs and startups through the maze of technological advancements.&#xA;Custom Software: Your Competitive Edge Why settle for one-size-fits-all solutions?&#xA;Deep Dive into Customisation: Tailor-made software that grows with you. Intellectual Property &amp;amp; R&amp;amp;D: Invest in your future, securing funding and innovation. AI Digital Marketing: Precision at Its Best Digital presence redefined. Think smarter, not harder.&#xA;Data-Driven Decisions: Crafting campaigns with surgical precision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank You For Contacting Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>We appreciate you taking the time to reach out. Your message has been successfully received.&#xA;Our team is reviewing your inquiry, and one of our experts will get back to you as soon as possible. We strive to respond to all queries within 24 hours.&#xA;If your matter is urgent, please feel free to contact us directly at:&#xA;Email: me@wajidkhan.info Phone: +44 020 3468 2115 In the meantime, you can explore our website for the latest insights on trademark and patent services, intellectual property protection, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trademark and Patent Services for Businesses and Startups</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/trademarks-and-patents-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/trademarks-and-patents-uk/</guid>
      <description>Our Trademark and Patent Services offer comprehensive protection for your innovations, ensuring that your ideas and brand identity are fully secured across a variety of sectors, from food recipes to AI robotics.&#xA;Protect Your Invention with 20 Years of Patent Security!&#xA;We Protect Your Innovations and Brand Identity We provide end-to-end trademark and patent services tailored to the unique needs of startups. From initial assessments to filings and strategic advice, our services are designed to ensure that your intellectual property is fully protected, allowing you to focus on growth and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>For expertise in building high-performance tech teams, evaluating startup technologies, auditing legacy software, and navigating trademarks, patents, and Digital Asset Protocols (DAPs), connect with Dr Wajid Khan.&#xA;Leverage strategic insights and tailored solutions to strengthen your business’s technological foundation and protect its intellectual property.&#xA;United Kingdom Dr Wajid Khan, Enterprise House, 5 Newtown Road, London-Luton Airport, LU1 3EA, United Kingdom.&#xA;Email: me@wajidkhan.info Call: +44 020 3468 2115 </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
